Guide to the Records of the American Institute of the City of New York for the Encouragement of Science and Invention 1808-1983 (bulk, 1828-1940) MS 17
New-York Historical Society
- Series I: Annual Fair Years, 1808-1930
  - Subseries 1: Annual Fairs, 1828-1926
    - Reports and Papers, 1st and 2nd Annual Fairs, 1828-1830, 1847 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - Judges Appointed for the Fair of 1830 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - "Bills 4th Annual Fair 1831" (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - Vouchers 4th Annual Fair, 1831 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - "Judges' Report - 5th Annual Fair - 1832" (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - "Judge's Reports 6th Annual Fair - 1833" (Offsite-box 1, Folder 6)
    - Minutes of the Managers of the 6th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1833 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 7)
    - "Bills 6th Annual Fair", 1833-1834 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 8)
    - "Judge's Reports of the 7th Annual Fair - 1834" (Offsite-box 1, Folder 9)
    - "Judge's Reports - 8th Annual Fair - 1835" (Offsite-box 1, Folder 10)
    - "Judge's Reports 9th Annual Fair 1836" (Offsite-box 1, Folder 11)
    - "Judge's Reports 10th Annual Fair 1837" (Offsite-box 1, Folder 12)
    - "Judge's Reports 11th Annual Fair 1838" (Offsite-box 2, Folder 1)
    - "Judge's Report - 12th Annual Fair 1839" (Offsite-box 2, Folder 2)
    - "Judge's Report - 12th Annual Fair 1839 - 13th Fair - Agricultural Reports - 1839" (Offsite-box 2, Folder 3)
    - "Reports - 12th Annual Fair - 1839 Managers of Committees" (Offsite-box 2, Folder 4)
    - "Vouchers 12th Fair 1839", 1839-1841 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 5)
    - "Judge's Reports: 13th Annual Fair 1840" (Offsite-box 2, Folder 6)
    - Judges Reports: "13th Fair 1840, Agricultural Reports" (Offsite-box 2, Folder 7)
    - "Reports - 13th Annual Fair 1840", 1839-1840 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 8)
    - "13th Annual Fair - Vouchers - 1840", 1839-1840 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 9)
    - "14th Fair Vouchers - 1841" (14th Fair Bills/ Premiums/ Arrangements/ Printing and Adr/ Ann Adr/ Com. on Finance), 1841 (1 of 2) (Offsite-box 2, Folder 10)
    - "14th Fair Vouchers 1841", 1841 (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 2, Folder 11)
    - "Judge's Report - 14th Annual Fair - 1841", 1841 (1 of 2) (Offsite-box 3, Folder 1)
    - "Judge's Report - 14th Annual Fair - 1841", 1841 (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 3, Folder 2)
    - "Reports - 14th Annual Fair Managers and Committees", 1841 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 3)
    - "Judge's Reports 15th Annual Fair 1842 - Agricultural Reports 15th Annual Fair 1842" (Offsite-box 3, Folder 4)
    - "Judge's Reports 15th Annual Fair 1842 - Mechanical Reports 15th Annual Fair 1842" (Offsite-box 3, Folder 5)
    - "Medal Awards - 1842", 1842-1843 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 6)
    - Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 15th Annual Fair 1842 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 7)
    - "Reports, 15th Annual Fair 1842 Managers and Committees" (Offsite-box 3, Folder 8)
    - "15th Fair Vouchers 1842", 1842-1843 (1 of 2) (Offsite-box 3, Folder 9)
    - "15th Fair Vouchers", 1842-1843 (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 3, Folder 10)
    - "Judges Agricultural Reports - 1843" (Offsite-box 3, Folder 11)
    - "Judge's Reports 16th Annual Fair 1843", 1843 (1 of 2) (Offsite-box 4, Folder 1)
    - "Judges Reports 16th Annual Fair 1843", 1843 (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 4, Folder 2)
    - "Reports, 16th Annual Fair 1843, Managers and Committees" (Offsite-box 4, Folder 3)
    - "16th Fair Vouchers - 1843", 1843 (1 of 2) (Offsite-box 4, Folder 4)
    - "Judges Reports 17th Fair 1844, 18th Fair 1845", 1844 (1 of 2) (Offsite-box 4, Folder 5)
    - "Judges Reports 17th Fair 1844, 18th Fair 1845", 1844 (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 4, Folder 6)
    - "Medal Awards - 1844", 1843-1845 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 7)
    - Premiums - 17th Annual Fair of the American Institute - 1844 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 8)
    - "Reports Agricultural 17th Annual Fair 1844" (Offsite-box 4, Folder 9)
    - "Reports, 17th Annual Fair, 1844, Managers and Committees" (Offsite-box 4, Folder 10)
    - "17th Fair Vouchers 1844", 1844-1845 (1 of 2) (Offsite-box 4, Folder 11)
    - "17th Fair Vouchers 1844", 1844-1845 (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 5, Folder 1)
    - "Agricultural Reports 18th Annual Fair 1845" (Offsite-box 5, Folder 2)
    - Judges' Reports 18th Annual Fair 1845, 1845 (1 of 2) (Offsite-box 5, Folder 3)
    - Judges' Reports 18th Annual Fair 1845, 1845 (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 5, Folder 4)
    - Premiums - 18th Fair - Agricultural and Horticultural, 1845 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 5)
    - "Reports 18th Annual Fair 1845 Managers and Committees" (Offsite-box 5, Folder 6)
    - "18th Fair Vouchers 1845", 1845-1846 (1 of 2) (Offsite-box 5, Folder 7)
    - "18th Fair Vouchers - 1845", 1845-1846 (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 5, Folder 8)
    - "19th Fair Committee on Arrangements 1846" (Offsite-box 5, Folder 9)
    - Judges' Reports - 19th Fair of the American Institute - 1846, 1846 (1 of 3) (Offsite-box 5, Folder 10)
    - Medal Awards, 1845-1846 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 9)
    - Judges' Reports - 19th Fair of the American Institute - 1846, 1846 (2 of 3) (Offsite-box 6, Folder 1)
    - Judges' Reports - 19th Fair of the American Institute - 1846, 1846 (3 of 3) (Offsite-box 6, Folder 2)
    - "Medal Awards - 1846", 1846-1848 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 3)
    - "Reports 19th Annual Fair, 1846, Managers and Committees", 1846-1847 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 4)
    - Vouchers for 19th Annual Fair of Institute, 1846 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 5)
    - "Agricultural Reports - 20th Fair - 1847" (Offsite-box 6, Folder 6)
    - Judges' Reports - 20th Annual Fair 1847 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 7)
    - "Reports 20th Annual Fair - 1847 - Managers and Committees" (Offsite-box 6, Folder 8)
    - "20th Fair Vouchers 1847", 1847-1848 (1 of 2) (Offsite-box 6, Folder 9)
    - "20th Fair Vouchers 1847", 1847-1848 (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 6, Folder 10)
    - "Judges Reports, 21st Annual Fair, 1848", 1848 (1 of 3) (Offsite-box 7, Folder 1)
    - "Judges Reports 21st Fair 1848", 1848 (2 of 3) (Offsite-box 7, Folder 2)
    - "Judges Report, 21st Fair 1848", 1848 (3 of 3) (Offsite-box 7, Folder 3)
    - "Medal Awards - 1848", 1848-1850 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 4)
    - "Reports 21st Annual Fair 1848 Managers and Committees", 1848-1849 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 5)
    - "21st Fair Vouchers, 1848", 1848-1849 (1 of 2) (Offsite-box 7, Folder 6)
    - "21st Fair Vouchers, 1848", 1848-1849 (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 7, Folder 7)
    - "Reports of Judges, 22nd Fair 1849", 1849 (1 of 3) (Offsite-box 7, Folder 8)
    - "Reports of Judges, 22nd Fair 1849", 1849 (2 of 3) (Offsite-box 7, Folder 9)
    - "Reports of Judges, 22nd Fair 1849", 1849 (3 of 3) (Offsite-box 8, Folder 1)
    - Report of the Managers, 22nd Fair, 1849, 1849-1850 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 2)
    - "Medal Award 1849", 1849-1850 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 3)
    - "22nd Fair Vouchers 1849", 1849-1850 (1 of 2) (Offsite-box 8, Folder 4)
    - "22nd Fair Vouchers 1849", 1849-1850 (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 8, Folder 5)
    - "Reports of Judges, 23d Fair, 1850", 1850 (1 of 3) (Offsite-box 8, Folder 6)
    - "Reports of Judges, 23d Fair, 1850", 1850 (2 of 3) (Offsite-box 8, Folder 7)
    - "Reports of Judges, 23d Fair, 1850", 1850 (3 of 3) (Offsite-box 8, Folder 8)
    - "Medal Award 1850", 1850-1851 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 1)
    - "Reports of the Managers 23rd Fair - 1850" (Offsite-box 9, Folder 2)
    - "Report of the Judges on Machinery and Models of the 23rd Annual Fair of the American Institute", 1850 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 3)
    - "23rd Fair Vouchers 1850", 1850 (1 of 2) (Offsite-box 9, Folder 4)
    - "23rd Fair Vouchers 1850", 1850 (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 9, Folder 5)
    - "Report of Judges 24th Fair 1851", 1851 (1 of 3) (Offsite-box 9, Folder 6)
    - "Reports of Judges, 24th Fair 1851", 1851 (2 of 3) (Offsite-box 9, Folder 7)
    - "Report of Judges 24th Fair 1851", 1851 (3 of 3) (Offsite-box 9, Folder 8)
    - "Report of the Judges on Agriculture and Horticulture Twenty-fourth Annual Fair of the American Institute, October, 1851" (Offsite-box 9, Folder 9)
    - "Medal Awards 1851", 1851-1852 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 1)
    - Report of the Managers 24th Annual Fair 1851 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 2)
    - "24th Fair Vouchers 1851", 1850-1852 (1 of 2) (Offsite-box 10, Folder 3)
    - "24th Fair Vouchers 1851", 1850-1852 (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 10, Folder 4)
    - "Reports of Judges, 25th Fair 1852", 1852 (1 of 3) (Offsite-box 10, Folder 5)
    - "Reports of Judges, 25th Fair 1852", 1852 (2 of 3) (Offsite-box 10, Folder 6)
    - "Report of Judges, 25th Fair 1852", 1852 (3 of 3) (Offsite-box 10, Folder 7)
    - "Reports of the Managers, 25th Annual Fair 1852" (Offsite-box 10, Folder 8)
    - "Medal Awards - 1852", 1852-1853 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 9)
    - "25th Fair Vouchers 1852", 1852 (1 of 2) (Offsite-box 10, Folder 10)
    - "25th Fair Vouchers 1852", 1852-1853 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 1)
    - "Reports of Judges 26th Fair 1853", 1853 (1 of 2) (Offsite-box 11, Folder 2)
    - "Reports of Judges 26th Fair 1853", 1853 (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 11, Folder 3)
    - "Medal Awards 1853", 1853-1854 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 4)
    - "Report of the Managers 26th Annual Fair 1853" (Offsite-box 11, Folder 5)
    - "26th Fair Vouchers 1853", 1853 (1 of 2) (Offsite-box 11, Folder 6)
    - "26th Fair Vouchers, 1853", 1853 (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 11, Folder 7)
    - "Reports of Judges 27th Fair 1855", 1855 (1 of 3) (Offsite-box 11, Folder 8)
    - "Reports of Judges 27th Fair 1855", 1855 (2 of 3) (Offsite-box 12, Folder 1)
    - "Reports of Judges 27th Fair 1855", 1855 (3 of 3) (Offsite-box 12, Folder 2)
    - Judges' Reports - 27th Annual Fair (No. 1), 1855 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 3)
    - Judges' Reports - 27th Annual Fair (No. 2), 1855 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 4)
    - Judges' Reports - 27th Annual Fair (No. 3), 1855 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 5)
    - Judges' Reports - 27th Annual Fair (No. 4), 1855 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 6)
    - "Medal Awards 1855", 1855-1856 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 7)
    - Premiums - 27th Annual Fair - 1855 (No. 1, No. 2, [No. 3], No. 4) (Offsite-box 12, Folder 8)
    - "27th Fair Vouchers 1855", 1855 (1 of 3) (Offsite-box 12, Folder 9)
    - "27th Fair Vouchers 1855", 1855 (2 of 3) (Offsite-box 13, Folder 1)
    - "27th Fair Vouchers 1855", 1855 (3 of 3) (Offsite-box 13, Folder 2)
    - Judges' Reports - 28th Fair - 1856, 1856 (1 of 3) (Offsite-box 13, Folder 3)
    - Judges' Reports - 28th Fair - 1856, 1856 (2 of 3) (Offsite-box 13, Folder 4)
    - Judges' Reports - 28th Fair - 1856, 1856 (3 of 3) (Offsite-box 13, Folder 5)
    - Judges' Reports - 28th Fair of the American Institute - Agricultural Report, 1856 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 6)
    - "Medal Awards 1856" (Offsite-box 13, Folder 7)
    - "Gold Medals Certified", 1856 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 8)
    - Premium Committee - 28th Annual Fair - 1856 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 9)
    - "Report of the Managers 28th Annual Fair 1856" (Offsite-box 13, Folder 10)
    - "28th Fair Vouchers 1856", 1856 (1 of 2) (Offsite-box 13, Folder 11)
    - "28th Fair Vouchers 1856", 1856 (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 14, Folder 1)
    - "Reports of Judges 29th Fair 1857", 1857 (1 of 3) (Offsite-box 14, Folder 2)
    - "Reports of the Judges 29th Fair 1857", 1857 (2 of 3) (Offsite-box 14, Folder 3)
    - "Report of the Judges, 29th Fair 1857", 1857 (3 of 3) (Offsite-box 14, Folder 4)
    - "29th Fair Vouchers, 1857", 1857 (1 of 3) (Offsite-box 14, Folder 5)
    - "29th Fair Vouchers 1857", 1857 (2 of 3) (Offsite-box 14, Folder 6)
    - "29th Fair Vouchers 1857", 1857 (3 of 3) (Offsite-box 14, Folder 7)
    - "Reports - 31st Fair 1859, Finance Committee 29th Fair 1857, 32nd Fair 1860, 36th Fair 1865, Premium Committee, 30th Fair 1858", 1857-1860, 1865 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 1)
    - "Reports of Judges 30th Fair 1858" (Offsite-box 15, Folder 2)
    - Committees - 30th Fair, 1858 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 3)
    - "30th Fair Vouchers 1858" (Offsite-box 15, Folder 4)
    - "Reports of Judges 31st Fair 1859", 1859 (1 of 2) (Offsite-box 15, Folder 5)
    - "Reports of Judges 31st Fair 1859", 1859 (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 15, Folder 6)
    - "Report of the Judges" (Agricultural Fair 1859) (Offsite-box 15, Folder 7)
    - "Reports of Judges - Horticultural Exhibition 31st Fair 1859 Palace Garden" (Offsite-box 15, Folder 8)
    - "31st Fair Vouchers 1859", 1859 (1 of 2) (Offsite-box 15, Folder 9)
    - "31st Fair Vouchers 1859", 1859 (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 15, Folder 10)
    - "Reports of Judges, 32nd Fair, 1860" (Offsite-box 15, Folder 11)
    - Reports and Papers - 32nd Fair, 1860 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 1)
    - "32nd Fair Vouchers 1860" (Offsite-box 16, Folder 2)
    - Reports and Papers - the American Institute re: Silver Medal, 1862 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 3)
    - Judges' Reports - 35th Fair, 1863 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 4)
    - Reports and Papers - 35th Fair, 1863 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 5)
    - "Rough Minutes of the Board of Managers 35 Fair 1863 - Academy of Music" (Offsite-box 16, Folder 6)
    - "35th Fair Vouchers 1863", 1863 (1 of 2) (Offsite-box 16, Folder 7)
    - "35th Fair Vouchers 1863", 1863 (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 16, Folder 8)
    - "Reports of Judges 36th Annual Fair - American Institute 1865 - Manufactures", 1865 (1 of 2) (Offsite-box 16, Folder 9)
    - "Reports of Judges 36th Annual Fair - American Institute 1865 - Manufactures", 1865 (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 16, Folder 10)
    - "Report of Committee on Printing and Publication of the 36th Annual Exhibition - 1865" (Offsite-box 16, Folder 11)
    - "36th Fair Vouchers 1865", 1865 (1 of 2) (Offsite-box 17, Folder 1)
    - "36th Fair Vouchers 1865", 1865 (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 17, Folder 2)
    - Reports and Papers - Board of Managers of Annual Fair, 1868 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 3)
    - "Judges' Reports - 37th Fair Depart 1, 1867" (Offsite-box 17, Folder 4)
    - "Judges' Reports - 37th Fair, Dept. 2, 1867", 1867 (1 of 2) (Offsite-box 17, Folder 5)
    - "Judges' Reports - 37th Fair, Dept. 2, 1867", 1867 (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 17, Folder 6)
    - "Judges' Reports - 37th Fair, Depart 3, 1867" (Offsite-box 17, Folder 7)
    - "Judges' Reports - 37th Fair Depart. 4, 1867" (Offsite-box 17, Folder 8)
    - "Judges' Reports - 37th Fair - Depart 5 - 1867" (Offsite-box 17, Folder 9)
    - "Judges' Reports - 37th Fair Depart. 6, 1867" (Offsite-box 17, Folder 10)
    - Judges' Reports - 37th Fair, Depart 7, 1867 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 1)
    - Reports and Papers - 37th Fair, 1867 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 2)
    - "37th Fair, Vouchers, 1867", 1867 (1 of 3) (Offsite-box 18, Folder 3)
    - "37th Fair, Vouchers, 1867", 1867 (2 of 3) (Offsite-box 18, Folder 4)
    - "37th Fair, Vouchers, 1867", 1867 (3 of 3) (Offsite-box 18, Folder 5)
    - 38th Fair "Report of Judges - Department 1, 1869" (Offsite-box 18, Folder 6)
    - 38th Fair "Report of Judges, Department 2, 1869" (Offsite-box 18, Folder 7)
    - 38th Fair "Report of Judges - Department 3, 1869" (Offsite-box 18, Folder 8)
    - 38th Fair "Report of Judges, Dept 4, 1869" (Offsite-box 18, Folder 9)
    - 38th Fair " Report of Judges - Department 5, 1869", 1869 (1 of 2) (Offsite-box 18, Folder 10)
    - 38th Fair "Report of Judges, Dept. 5, 1869", 1869-1870 (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 18, Folder 11)
    - 38th Fair "Report of Judges, Dept 6, 1869" (Offsite-box 19, Folder 1)
    - 38th Fair "Report of Judges - Department 7, 1869" (Offsite-box 19, Folder 2)
    - "Reports 38th Fair - 1869" (Offsite-box 19, Folder 3)
    - "Reports Finance and Ticket Committees 38th, 39th and 42nd, 1869, '70, '73" (Offsite-box 19, Folder 4)
    - "38th Fair, Vouchers 1869", 1869 (1 of 4) (Offsite-box 19, Folder 5)
    - "38th Fair, Vouchers 1869", 1869 (2 of 4) (Offsite-box 19, Folder 6)
    - "38th Fair, Vouchers 1869", 1869 (3 of 4) (Offsite-box 19, Folder 7)
    - "38th Fair, Vouchers 1869", 1869-1870 (4 of 4) (Offsite-box 19, Folder 8)
    - Judges' Reports - 39th Fair of the American Institute - 1, 1870 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 9)
    - Judges' Reports - 39th Fair of the American Institute - 2, 1870 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 10)
    - Judges' Reports - 39th Fair of the American Institute - 3, 1870 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 1)
    - Judges' Reports - 39th Fair of the American Institute - 4, 1870 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 2)
    - Judges' Reports - 39th Fair of the American Institute - 5, 1870 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 3)
    - Judges' Reports - 39th Fair of the American Institute - 6, 1870 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 4)
    - Judges' Reports - 39th Fair of the American Institute - 7, 1870 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 5)
    - "Reports 39th Fair 1870" (Offsite-box 20, Folder 6)
    - Reports and Papers - 39th Fair, 1870 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 7)
    - "Reports Finance and Ticket Committees 38th, 39th and 42nd, 1869, '70, '73", 1870 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 8)
    - "39th Fair, Vouchers, 1870", 1870 (1 of 4) (Offsite-box 20, Folder 9)
    - "39th Fair Vouchers 1870", 1870 (2 of 4) (Offsite-box 20, Folder 10)
    - "39th Fair Vouchers, 1870", 1870 (3 of 4) (Offsite-box 20, Folder 11)
    - "39th Fair Vouchers, 1870", 1870 (4 of 4) (Offsite-box 21, Folder 1)
    - "Judges' Report 40th Exhibition American Institute 1871 - 1" (Offsite-box 21, Folder 2)
    - "Judges Reports, 40th Exhibition, 1871 - 2", 1871 (1 of 3) (Offsite-box 21, Folder 3)
    - "Judges Reports, 40th Exhibit, 1871 - 2", 1871 (2 of 3) (Offsite-box 21, Folder 4)
    - "Judges' Reports, 40th Exhibition, 1871 - 2", 1871 (3 of 3) (Offsite-box 21, Folder 5)
    - "Judges' Report 40th Exhibition American Institute 1871, III" (Offsite-box 21, Folder 6)
    - "Judges Report 40th Exhibition American Institute 1871 - IV" (Offsite-box 21, Folder 7)
    - "Judges' Report 40th Exhibition American Institute 1871 - V", 1871 (1 of 2) (Offsite-box 22, Folder 1)
    - "Judges Report, 40th Exhibit, American Institute 1871 - V", 1871 (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 22, Folder 2)
    - "Judges' Report - 40th Exhibition, American Institute 1871 - VI" (Offsite-box 22, Folder 3)
    - "Judges Reports, 40th Exhibit 1871 - VII" (Offsite-box 22, Folder 4)
    - "Reports 40th Fair 1871" (Offsite-box 22, Folder 5)
    - "Reports and Papers American Institute 40th Fair 1871", 1871-1872 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 6)
    - "40th Fair Vouchers 1871", 1871 (1 of 3) (Offsite-box 22, Folder 7)
    - "40th Fair Vouchers 1871", 1871 (2 of 3) (Offsite-box 23, Folder 1)
    - "40th Fair Vouchers 1871", 1871 (3 of 3) (Offsite-box 23, Folder 2)
    - Judges' Reports - 41st Fair of the American Institute - 1, 1872 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 3)
    - Judges' Reports - 41st Fair of the American Institute - 2, 1872 (1 of 2) (Offsite-box 23, Folder 4)
    - Judges' Reports - 41st Fair of the American Institute - 2, 1872 (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 23, Folder 5)
    - Judges' Reports - 41st Fair of the American Institute - 3, 1872 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 6)
    - Judges' Reports - 41st Fair of the American Institute - 4, 1872 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 1)
    - Judges' Reports - 41st Fair of the American Institute - 5, 1872 (1 of 2) (Offsite-box 24, Folder 2)
    - Judges' Reports - 41st Fair of the American Institute - 5, 1872 (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 24, Folder 3)
    - Judges' Reports - 41st Fair of the American Institute - 6, 1872 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 4)
    - Judges' Reports - 41st Fair of the American Institute - 7, 1872 (1 of 2) (Offsite-box 24, Folder 5)
    - Judges' Reports - 41st Fair of the American Institute - 7, 1872 (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 24, Folder 6)
    - "Reports 41st Fair 1872" (Offsite-box 24, Folder 7)
    - "Reports and Papers American Institute 1872 (41st Fair)" (Offsite-box 25, Folder 1)
    - "41st Fair Vouchers 1872", 1872 (1 of 3) (Offsite-box 25, Folder 2)
    - "41st Fair Vouchers 1872", 1872 (2 of 3) (Offsite-box 25, Folder 3)
    - "41st Fair Vouchers 1872", 1872 (3 of 3) (Offsite-box 25, Folder 4)
    - "Vouchers, 41st Fair, 1872", 1872 (1 of 3) (Offsite-box 25, Folder 5)
    - "Vouchers 41st Fair 1872", 1872 (2 of 3) (Offsite-box 25, Folder 6)
    - "Vouchers, 41st Fair, 1872", 1872 (3 of 3) (Offsite-box 25, Folder 7)
    - "Reports and Papers American Institute 1873 (42nd Fair)", 1872-1874 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 1)
    - "Reports Finance and Ticket Committees 38th, 39th, 42nd, 1869, '70, '73", 1873 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 2)
    - "42nd Fair Vouchers 1873", 1873 (1 of 2) (Offsite-box 26, Folder 3)
    - "42nd Fair, Vouchers 1873", 1873 (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 26, Folder 4)
    - "42nd Fair Vouchers 1873", 1873 (1 of 2) (Offsite-box 26, Folder 5)
    - "42nd Fair Vouchers 1873", 1873 (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 26, Folder 6)
    - Judges' Reports "43rd Fair 1874 (1)" (Offsite-box 27, Folder 1)
    - Judges' Reports "43rd Fair 1874 (2)", 1874 (1 of 2) (Offsite-box 27, Folder 2)
    - Judges' Reports "43rd Fair 1874 (2)", 1874 (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 27, Folder 3)
    - Judges' Reports 43rd Fair "3", 1874 (1 of 2) (Offsite-box 27, Folder 4)
    - Judges' Reports - 43rd Fair "3", 1874 (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 27, Folder 5)
    - Judges' Reports - 43rd Exhibition of the American Institute - 4, 1874 (1 of 2) (Offsite-box 27, Folder 6)
    - Judges' Reports - 43rd Exhibition of the American Institute - 4, 1874 (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 28, Folder 1)
    - Judges' Reports 43rd Exhibition 1874 "5", 1874 (1 of 3) (Offsite-box 28, Folder 2)
    - Judges' Reports 43rd Exhibition 1874 "5", 1874 (2 of 3) (Offsite-box 28, Folder 3)
    - Judges' Reports 43rd Exhibition 1874: "5", 1874-1875 (3 of 3) (Offsite-box 28, Folder 4)
    - Judges' Reports - 43rd Exhibition of the American Institute - 6, 1874 (1 of 2) (Offsite-box 28, Folder 5)
    - Judges' Reports - 43rd Exhibition of the American Institute - 6, 1874 (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 28, Folder 6)
    - Judges' Reports - 43rd Exhibition of the American Institute - 7, 1874 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 7)
    - "Reports 43rd Fair American Institute 1874", 1874-1875 (Offsite-box 29, Folder 1)
    - "Daily Reports Finance Committee 43rd Annual Fair American Institute 1874" (Offsite-box 29, Folder 2)
    - "Daily Reports Ticket Committee 43 Annual Fair American Institute 1874" (Offsite-box 29, Folder 3)
    - "Log of Rotary Engines, tested at the 43rd Exhibition, 1874" (Offsite-box 29, Folder 4)
    - 43rd Fair - Notes, Lists, 1874 (Offsite-box 29, Folder 5)
    - "43rd Fair of the American Institute - Vouchers - 1874", 1874 (1 of 3) (Offsite-box 29, Folder 6)
    - "43rd Fair of the American Institute - Vouchers - 1874", 1874 (2 of 3) (Offsite-box 29, Folder 7)
    - "43rd Fair of the American Institute Vouchers - 1874", 1874 (3 of 3) (Offsite-box 29, Folder 8)
    - "43rd Fair Vouchers 1874", 1874 (1 of 2) (Offsite-box 29, Folder 9)
    - "43rd Fair, Vouchers, 1874", 1874 (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 30, Folder 1)
    - Vouchers - 43rd Fair of the American Institute, 1874 (Offsite-box 30, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence - 44th Fair, 1875 (Offsite-box 30, Folder 3)
    - "Daily Reports Finance Committee 44th Annual Fair American Institute - 1875" (Offsite-box 30, Folder 4)
    - "Daily Reports Ticket Committee 44th Annual Fair American Institute 1875" (Offsite-box 30, Folder 5)
    - "Reports 44th Fair 1875" (Offsite-box 30, Folder 6)
    - "Reports and Papers American Institute 1875 (44th)" (Offsite-box 30, Folder 7)
    - "44th Fair Vouchers - 1875", 1875 (1 of 2) (Offsite-box 30, Folder 8)
    - "44th Fair Vouchers - 1875", 1875 (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 30, Folder 9)
    - "44th Fair Vouchers 1875", 1875-1876 (1 of 3) (Offsite-box 31, Folder 1)
    - "44th Fair Vouchers 1875", 1875 (2 of 3) (Offsite-box 31, Folder 2)
    - "44th Fair Vouchers 1875", 1875 (3 of 3) (Offsite-box 31, Folder 3)
    - "Reports 45th Fair 1876" (Offsite-box 31, Folder 4)
    - "Daily Reports, Finance Committee, 45 Annual Fair American Institute 1876" (Offsite-box 31, Folder 5)
    - "Daily Reports, Ticket Committee, 45 Annual Fair American Institute 1876" (Offsite-box 31, Folder 6)
    - "45th Fair Vouchers 1876", 1876-1877 (1 of 3) (Offsite-box 31, Folder 7)
    - "45th Fair Vouchers 1876", 1876 (2 of 3) (Offsite-box 32, Folder 1)